We are grateful
for this schedule adjustment,
which gives us more chance to gather
and talk about the scriptures.
One of the most powerful places
for gospel learning is the home.
It is even more
important than our classrooms.
This schedule adjustment is
a meaningful opportunity
to strengthen gospel learning at home
and focus more fully on Jesus Christ.
Come, Follow Me reminds us
that the purpose of gospel learning is
to deepen our conversion and help
us become more like the Savior.
The new schedule is designed
to support the daily home-centered
efforts already taking place.
As we study the scriptures at home
and talk about what
we're learning at church,
the gospel becomes more
personal and part of everyday life.
When learning begins in the home
and is strengthened at church,
it blesses individuals,
families, and entire wards and branches.
That's why our Sunday School
time matters so much.
Now, watch as this teacher models
how we can focus on Jesus Christ
and support gospel learning at home.
A common misconception is that if
you are a teacher, you are the talker.
You are all knowledgeable.
Welcome to Sunday School today.
I am so excited to hear what
you guys have learned from Come,
Follow Me and from Isaiah.
By a show of hands, who was able
to read from Isaiah this week?
Awesome. That's great.
Now, to help you remember what you
might have studied during the week,
I've written up some of the doctrine,
as well as this question: What did
you learn this week about the Savior?
And I would love
to hear your thoughts on this.
To help you remember what
you've learned and studied,
I'm going to give you a couple seconds
to look back in your scriptures,
look at any notes, and then I'm
gonna give you the opportunity to share
with the person sitting next to you.
So go ahead and take just a little
bit to remember what it is that you
studied this week. In Come, Follow Me,
it really encourages teachers
to be the facilitator,
to create opportunities for people
to share what they are learning.
I am a strong believer
that if I am the only one talking
and sharing what I am learning
in the scriptures,
the class is not nearly
as meaningful and rich as it could be.
I always, in every class,
try to invite class members
to share what they are studying
and learning about Jesus Christ
in their personal
and family scripture study.
I heard some wonderful comments out there,
and I would love to have you
share if you feel comfortable
with the class. Do we have anyone
that would like to start us off?
President D. Todd Christofferson declared,
"The central purpose of all
scripture is to fill our souls with faith
in God the Father
and in His Son, Jesus Christ.
The message and spiritual power
of the scriptures lead us to salvation.
Our decision to read and study
the scriptures is an important
step toward becoming like
Heavenly Father and Jesus Christ."
The home is the center of gospel learning,
and Sunday School is meant
to support what's happening there.
Sunday School involves
discussion and learning from others.
It is not just
a presentation by a teacher.
Teachers don't need to cover
every part of the lesson.
Instead, invite others to share
their thoughts and testimonies.
As we prepare each week by studying
the scriptures at home and using the Come,
Follow Me resource, we can learn
with the Spirit guiding the conversation
at church, helping us
learn from one another.
Because class time is limited,
it's important to begin promptly and focus
on the teachings, example,
sacrifice, and love of Jesus Christ.
Every minute matters.